SHIVA PRASAD GATTAIAHGARI

CONTACT



+919502863711



Shivaghatts@gmail.com



H- NO 11-78, IDA Bollaram,

Hyderabad, 502325.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

- Master's in Business
 Administration in Warsaw
 Management University.
 (March 2022- February 2024).
- Bachelor's in Commerce from Gandhi Institute of Management University.

SKILLS

- CONTRACT NEGOTIATION
- STRATEGIC SOURCING
- RISK MANAGEMENT
- INVENTORY MANAGEMENT
- ANALYTICAL SKILLS
- MASTER DATA
- ERP
- CLIENT REQUIREMENTS
- ORDER-TO- CASH

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- SAP S/4 HANA (Material Management)
- Microsoft Dynamics Navision
- Focus 3
- Advanced Excel

LANGUAGES

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Initiative-taking Individual with a high spirit to lead, Communicate and Organize a team in an Efficient manner. I am a Supply chain professional with over five years of diverse experience in Manufacturing industry. Have a proven record of building resilient and responsive supply chains with a focus on continuous improvements and digitalization. Skilled in managing high-scale projects and enthusiastic about making operations leaner, simpler, and sustainable. I am looking for challenging opportunities to gain experience and enhance my skills.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Inventory and Supply Chain Manager - 02/2021 to 03/2022 **PATIL RAIL INFRASTRUCTURE PRIVATE LIMITED**, Hyderabad, India.

- Configuration and Maintenance of Mater Data.
- Customization and Maintenance of Inventory Management.
- Collaborated with cross country officials to procure CAPEX and project material to setup an Industry. Reduced lead time by 40% by establishing ordering and delivery schedule system.
- Prepared monthly purchase plans in advance to avoid the overflow of the Budget.
- Monitoring all the Entries in SAP from raising PR, PO, Receipt of Materials, payment to the Vendors, issuing the materials, and stock updating. Exploring cost saving techniques and reduce procurement cost.

E-COMMERCE AND LOGISTICS MENTOR- 10/2020 to 02/2021 **QUESS CORP PRIVATE LIMITED**, Bangalore, India.

- Taught to Graduate students about Supply Chain Management, Logistics and Customer Service.
- Conducted Mock Interviews and gave feedback on their performance.

Store In Charge - 01/2020 to 09/2020

PANDROL RAHEE TECHNOLOGIES PRIVATE LIMITED, Hyderabad, India.

- Negotiating contracts with suppliers, vendors, contractors, and customers.
- Managing day-to-day cooperation with a portfolio of international approved suppliers for fulfilling the needs of both internal and external customers to implement Procurement Strategy.
- Maintained good relationship with the Vendors and Clients to resolve disputes in a strategic manner.
- Distribution of Finished goods to USA, Europe and Australia.
- Ensured to meet the International Guidelines in terms of packaging and documentation for Exports and Imports.

Inventory Store Assistant - 02/2012 to 10/2016 SYSL PHARMA PRIVATE LIMITED, Hyderabad, India.

- Monitoring and maintaining current inventory levels; processing purchasing orders as required.
- Recording purchases, performing physical count of inventory, and reconciles actual stock count to computer-generated reports.
- Served as a cashier and handled cash and cash-related payments.